▍2026 辛辛那提 ATP1000 1/4决赛
蒂亚福 7-6(2) 7-5 穆塞蒂 · 赛后场上采访
Francis, congratulations.
弗朗西斯 恭喜你
There's been lightning in the area,
这一带打雷了
there was electricity on the court tonight.
今晚球场上也是电光四射
Talk us through the last few games
跟我们说说最后几局
and how you managed those emotions.
你是怎么控制住情绪的
I thought I played a great first match point.
我觉得那分赛点打得不错
Missed the backhand,
反手打丢了
just overcooked the backhand,
反手发力太猛
had a pick up and you know got broken.
对手接了一拍 然后我被破发了
I did play a great game and break back.
但我马上打了一局 破回来了
So did I there at the end.
最后那一刻也是这样
I mean look, he's a hell of a player.
他真的是个厉害的选手
We've been at the top for a while.
我们都在这个位置打了挺久
He's gonna make you beat him
他会逼着你去赢下他
and that's what I did tonight.
而这就是我今晚做到的
What did you
你在这场比赛里
have to figure out strategically
战术上想清楚了什么
over the course of the match?
才走到这一步？
I just got to play the win.
我就是想着去赢下这场球
You know we're all long seasons.
整个赛季都很长
We're all just at one percent,
大家其实都差那么一点点
just trying to figure it out.
都在摸索怎么突破
Guy who just plays a little more brave
谁在关键时刻更敢打
at certain moments gets it
谁就能拿下
and I was hitting my shots great tonight.
今晚我击球状态很好
From back in the court I've
底线相持这块
been playing really well
我一直打得不错
so I was just counting on that.
所以就靠这个撑下来
You've been to the final here before.
你以前打进过这里的决赛
How much does that help you for what's
这段经历对你接下来
to come?
有多大帮助？
Every match is its own story,
每场比赛都是独立的故事
its own journey.
各走各的路
I'm just happy to be another semi,
能再进一次半决赛就很开心
get a chance to be in the final, hopefully.
希望还能有机会打进决赛
So I'm just gonna go out there and compete
接下来我就是全力去拼
as hard as I can and give myself a chance.
给自己争取一个机会
That's all I'm gonna do.
我能做的就是这些
Bravo.
真棒